module.exports = [
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'What does JSON stand for?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: 'Java Sound Omitting Node',
        b: 'JavaScript Object Notation',
        c: 'Juvenile Sea Orchid Narwhal',
        d: 'John Snow Order Nation'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'How many Platonic solids are there?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 5,
        b: 7,
        c: 666,
        d: 2
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'What does CSS stand for?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Cascading Style Sheets',
        b: 'Controverse Script Style',
        c: 'Converting Section Sheet',
        d: 'Comfortable Selfie Stick'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which is the correct order of releases for this Disney movies?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: 'Aladdin - Bambi - Mulan - Toy Story',
        b: 'Bambi - Aladdin - Toy Story - Mulan',
        c: 'Mulan - Bambi - Aladdin - Toy Story',
        d: 'Toy Story - Aladdin - Bambi - Mulan'e
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'In which year was the University in Hagenberg founded?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: '1990',
        b: '1996',
        c: '1989',
        d: '1993'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Grand Central Terminal, New York is the world\'s',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'largest railway station',
        b: 'highest railway station',
        c: 'longest railway station',
        d: 'None of these'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'For which of the following disciplines is the Nobel Prize awarded?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'Physics and Chemistry',
        b: 'Physiology or Medicine',
        c: 'Literature, Peace and Economics',
        d: 'All of these'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'What does the \'GR\' at the key \'ALT GR\' stand for?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: 'Alt Greek',
        b: 'Alt Graph',
        c: 'Alt Great',
        d: 'None of these'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Photophobia is',
        answer: 'c',
        a: 'the fear of being photographed',
        b: 'the ability to perceive light',
        c: 'abnormal intolerance of light',
        d: 'the fear of memory-flashbacks'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Penicillin was invented by',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'Dr Jonas E. Salk',
        b: 'Gregory Mendal',
        c: 'Paul Ehrlich',
        d: 'A. Fleming'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'The headquarter of International Atomic Energy Agency are situated at',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Vienna',
        b: 'Paris',
        c: 'Rome',
        d: 'Washington, D.C.'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'When was Mahatma Gandhi assassinated?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: '1951',
        b: '1948',
        c: '1958',
        d: '1971'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'When was Shakespeare born?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: '1564',
        b: '1618',
        c: '1642',
        d: '1776'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Where is the Eiffel Tower located in Paris?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: 'Bois de Boulogne',
        b: 'Champ de Mars',
        c: 'Jardin des Plantes',
        d: 'Parc de Belleville'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Who plays Lara Croft in the Tomb Raider movies?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Angelina Jolie',
        b: 'Minnie Driver',
        c: 'Nell McAndrew',
        d: 'Jennifer Aniston'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'How many figures are there in a completed Sudoku puzzle?',
        answer: 'c',
        a: '49',
        b: '64',
        c: '81',
        d: '100'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which Shakespeare character is known as the \'Moor of Venice\'?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'Hamlet',
        b: 'Julius Caesar',
        c: 'King Lear',
        d: 'Othello'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Who wrote the ballad \'Erlkönig\'?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Johann Wolfgang von Goethe',
        b: 'Joseph von Eichendorff',
        c: 'E.T.A. Hoffmann',
        d: 'Ludwik Richter'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'How many teeth do humans have in total?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: '36',
        b: '32',
        c: '24',
        d: '44'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Dipsomania is an uncontrollable craving for what?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Alcohol',
        b: 'Dipping sauces',
        c: 'Sea bathing',
        d: 'The green Teletubby'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Who directed Alien?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: 'Dietmar Rammerstorfer',
        b: 'Ridley Scott',
        c: 'Steven Spielberg',
        d: 'David Cronenberg'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'What is the largest food company measured by revenue?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'Tesla',
        b: 'Unilever',
        c: 'PepsiCo',
        d: 'Nestle'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these hands would have the lowest value in poker?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Three of a kind',
        b: 'Straight',
        c: 'Flush',
        d: 'Full house'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these movies made the most money in box office?',
        answer: 'c',
        a: 'The Dark Knight',
        b: 'Titanic',
        c: 'Avatar',
        d: 'Star Wars: Episode VII'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these movies made the least money in box office?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'The Dark Knight Rises',
        b: 'Inception',
        c: 'Guardians Of The Galaxy',
        d: 'Suicide Squad'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these cities has the most inhabitants?',
        answer: 'c',
        a: 'Berlin',
        b: 'Madrid',
        c: 'Saint Petersburg',
        d: 'Paris'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these cities has the least inhabitants?',
        answer: 'd',
        a: 'Minsk',
        b: 'Vienna',
        c: 'Budapest',
        d: 'Barcelona'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which of these companies did Facebook not buy?',
        answer: 'a',
        a: 'Behavio',
        b: 'WhatsApp',
        c: 'Hot Potato',
        d: 'Instagram'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'How old was Harry Potter when he first went to Hogwarts?',
        answer: 'c',
        a: '9',
        b: '10',
        c: '11',
        d: 'None of these'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'Which one of these is not a Belgian beer?',
        answer: 'c',
        a: 'Duvel',
        b: 'Leffe',
        c: 'Bavaria',
        d: 'Primus'
    },
    {
        type: 'choice',
        question: 'When was Star Wars: Episode V released?',
        answer: 'b',
        a: '1979',
        b: '1980',
        c: '2002',
        d: '2003'
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many approved cat breeds exists?',
        answer: 40
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How much is the meaning of life?',
        answer: 42
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'What is the percentage of nitrogen in the earth atmosphere?',
        answer: 78
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many humans are born approximately per hour?',
        answer: 15000
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'What is the gravitational acceleration on earth in m/s²?',
        answer: 9.81
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many partner universities are working with FH Upper Austria?',
        answer: 263
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many worker-bees are in a beehive in summer?',
        answer: 40000
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many countries are in the EU?',
        answer: 28
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many students are studying at FH Hagenberg?',
        answer: 1574
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many cities are there in Europe that have over a million inhabitants?',
        answer: 33
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many views does Gangnam style have on youtube?',
        answer: 2855164999
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many full length albums has Taylor Swift released?',
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many original songs have The Beatles released?',
        answer: 237
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many cards are there in a UNO deck?',
        answer: 108
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many tigers are currently still living in the wild?',
        answer: 3890
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many employees does Google have?',
        answer: 61814
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How much did Facebook pay to acquire WhatsApp?',
        answer: 19000000000
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many movies based on Tolkien\'s Middle Earth were made so far?',
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        type: 'estimate',
        question: 'How many actors appear in all 8 of the Harry Potter movies?',
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the working title of this game?',
        answer: 'Quodyssey'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who was the leading politician in favor of Brexit?',
        answer: 'Nigel Farage'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What\'s the name of the now already famous press secretary of the new president of the United States?',
        answer: 'Sean Spicer'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who is the founder of Tesla and SpaceX?',
        answer: 'Elon Musk'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who is the new French President?',
        answer: 'Emmanuel Macron'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which company is currently the market leader in cloud services?',
        answer: 'Amazon'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the name of the Katy Perry song featured in the movie The Interview?',
        answer: 'Fireworks'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which country won the European Championships in 2016?',
        answer: 'Portugal'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which country won the last World Cup in Brazil?',
        answer: 'Germany'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the of the athlete that won a gold medal for the 5000m and the 10000m at the last two Olympic Games?',
        answer: 'Mo Farah'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which country won the last World Cup in Brazil?',
        answer: 'Germany'
    },
    {
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which programming languge is most known for being named after a gem?',
        answer: 'Ruby'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Which IDE\'s name has a connection to the moon?',
        answer: 'Eclipse'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the name of the director of Inception?',
        answer: 'Christopher Nolan'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the name of the actor who plays Elrond in the lord of the rings?',
        answer: 'Hugo Weaving'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'In the Harry Potter series, what is the name of the famous Bulgarian seeker?',
        answer: 'Viktor Krum'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'In Game Of Thrones, what is the name of Daenerys\' brother?',
        answer: 'Viserys'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who portrays the delightful Francis Underwood in House of Cards?',
        answer: 'Kevin Spacey'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who is the voice of Darth Vader?',
        answer: 'James Earl Jones'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who played Deckard in Blade Runner?',
        answer: 'Harrison Ford'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What\'s the name of Mickey Mouse\'s wife?',
        answer: 'Minnie Mouse'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'Who is the voice of Donkey in the Shrek movies?',
        answer: 'Eddie Murphy'
    },
    { 
        type: 'open',
        question: 'What is the name of the layout of a french keyboard, it\'s not qwerty but?',
        answer: 'azerty'
    },
];